<!-- agent-office-vp:fix worker=0149babee058 kind=verify head=80f45405517c1c8db22c33052105b9a6d3fe8bf9 attempt=1 details=verify:related_tests -->
≡ƒº░ The VP asked Pixel at Desk 1 (office/pixel-0149) to fix it: related tests failed.

- The VP's check of the merge result failed at "related tests":

```
  ...
# Subtest: worker launch, restore, add-repo and safe default cleanup cover every repository
ok 443 - worker launch, restore, add-repo and safe default cleanup cover every repository
  ---
  duration_ms: 18553.9389
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: per-repository Changes sessions isolate same-named files and commit only the selected repository
ok 444 - per-repository Changes sessions isolate same-named files and commit only the selected repository
  ---
  duration_ms: 22081.8303
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: PR actions use the selected starting branches and each repo remote, with independent PRs
ok 445 - PR actions use the selected starting branches and each repo remote, with independent PRs
  ---
  duration_ms: 24515.0637
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: PR targets use the selected repository for HTTPS and SSH without forwarding URL credentials
ok 446 - PR targets use the selected repository for HTTPS and SSH without forwarding URL credentials
  ---
  duration_ms: 0.5615
  type: 'test'
  ...
# Subtest: explicit cleanup removes the selected worktrees and keeps branches or deletes both as requested
ok 447 - explicit cleanup removes the selected worktrees and keeps branches or deletes both as requested
  ---
  duration_ms: 11533.1415
  type: 'test'
  ...
1..447
# tests 447
# suites 0
# pass 425
# fail 21
# cancelled 0
# skipped 1
# todo 0
# duration_ms 279612.4107
```

The VP merges this PR on a later sweep once its check of the merge result passes. It won't start a second fix while this one is under way.
